{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Information Assurance & Security (Cybersecurity Fundamentals)",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "02 Handout 1 -- Security Objectives",
    "LastModified": "19 February 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "02 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData":  [
    {
      "question": "What is a set of rules that applies to activities for the computer and communications resources that belong to an organization?",
      "answer": "Security Policy",
      "choices": [
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Security Policy"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should describe how the effectiveness of security measures will be monitored?",
      "answer": "Security Policy",
      "choices": [
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Security Policy"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ensures that only authorized users can access objects on the system?",
      "answer": "Resource Protection",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Resource Protection"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the ability to secure all types of system resources refer to?",
      "answer": "Resource Protection",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Resource Protection"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance or verification that the resource (human or machine) at the other end of the session really is what it claims to be?",
      "answer": "Authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authorization",
        "Authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which security objective does digital certificates provide a more secure method refers to?",
      "answer": "Authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authorization",
        "Authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an assurance that the person or computer at the other end of the session has permission to carry out the request?",
      "answer": "Authorization",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is performed in context application?",
      "answer": "Authorization",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance that the arriving information is the same as what was sent out?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does understanding integrity require?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is protected from unauthorized changes or tampering?",
      "answer": "Data Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Data Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does data integrity defend against?",
      "answer": "Data Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Data Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What provides consistent and expected results with expected performance?",
      "answer": "System Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "System Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the proof that a transaction occurred, or that a user sent or received a message?",
      "answer": "Nonrepudiation",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Nonrepudiation"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance that sensitive information remains private and is not visible to an eavesdropper?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is critical to total data security?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What monitors security-relevant events to provide a log of both successful and unsuccessful (denied) access?",
      "answer": "Auditing Security Activities",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Auditing Security Activities"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What records tell who is doing what on the systems?",
      "answer": "Successful access",
      "choices": [
        "Unsuccessful access",
        "Graduating access",
        "Access Point",
        "Successful access"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What records tell either that someone is attempting to break the security or that someone is having difficulty accessing the system?",
      "answer": "Unsuccessful access",
      "choices": [
        "Unsuccessful access",
        "Graduating access",
        "Access Point",
        "Successful access"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    }
  ]
}